# Matt Mandersheid

Marquette, Michigan, United States

mmandersheid@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/matt-mandersheid-91a0b8a0

# **Summary**

As an IT Technician at Return, I provide software and hardware support for various clients, ranging from software installation and troubleshooting to account management and network configuration. I have 13 years of experience in IT support, both in-person and remote, and a bachelor's degree in Business Computer Information Systems.

I have a strong skillset in web development and SEO, using HTML, Javascript, CSS, and Python to create, maintain, and optimize websites for different purposes and audiences. I also have knowledge and experience in using various tools and platforms, such as Google Admin Console, Azure AD, PowerShell, MS Office, Sharepoint, Active Directory, SCCM, and Remote Desktop software. My goal is to deliver IT solutions that meet the needs and expectations of my clients and enhance their business performance.

# **Experience**

### R IT Technician

Return

Apr 2023 - Present (9 months)
Google Workspace administration

Device management

Rippling workforce management

JAMF administration (previous to Rippling)

Freshdesk service use

1Password administration

# IT Helpdesk

**TEKSystems** 

May 2022 - Sep 2022 (5 months)

Contract remote position supporting Trinity Health in software installation, software support and account troubleshooting.

ServiceNow ticketing software management.

Fielding up to 50 calls / day

Azure Multi-factor authentication configuration and setup.

Active Directory account support.

Workday account support.

Microsoft Office suite troubleshooting.

Healthstream account support.

# IT Technician (Software/Hardware)

Upper Peninsula Health Plan (UPHP)

Jan 2019 - Jun 2021 (2 years 6 months)

Imaged and supported custom work-from-home PC builds during COVID telecommuting.

Troubleshot desktops, laptops, and other mobile devices remotely and hands-on, face-to-face with end users, for issues ranging from networking, hardware, to software in a Windows 7 and Windows 10 environment.

Performed Mitel phone system management for end users, phone hardware upgrades.

Replaced, deployed, imaged, re-imaged, and performed break fix tasks on desktops, laptops, and tablets on Windows 7 and Windows 10.

Polycom support for in-house teleconferencing.

Provided Tier 1/Tier 2 technical support via phone, email, and ticketing software.

Reviewing account safety and security with staff to avoid phishing and email breaches.

Providing multi-factor authentication support to provide additional account security to end users.

Jointly managed UPHP Sharepoint site.

Troubleshot SFTP/FTP Filezilla issues for personnel.



### Remote Client Technology Technician

Mt. Hood Community College

Aug 2016 - May 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Project Lead for upgrading our remote desktop software to Goverlan.

Fielding approximately 20+ calls and emails per day on account access and security, software troubleshooting, hardware, and classroom support across campus.

Assisted with Papercut access groups, Blackboard support, PBX VOIP configuration and troubleshooting, Active Directory, Windows user profile troubleshooting.

Completed documentation on tickets by closing or escalating them in the correct manner utilizing our ticketing software.

Supporting issues ranging from account recovery to hardware and software issues across campus. Onboarded new employees and developed a new method for our onboarding process.

#### IT Technician

#### Cascade Computer Maintenance

Jan 2016 - Jul 2016 (7 months)

Utilized Kaseya for remote work, performed hardware support as an HP certified technician.

Contracted with Portland Public Schools and upgraded 15+ schools with AV projector cart rollouts.

Monitored Symantec Antivirus logs, Datto backup recovery, and MS Exchange systems for Portland clients.

In-house or on-site printer troubleshooting and support.

#### Hardware/Software Technician

#### Peninsula Infomed

Jun 2010 - Nov 2015 (5 years 6 months)

Began as an Intern/remained as permanent position.

Worked extensively with Misys Tiger, Misys EMR, and other EHR software.

Patch panel, VLAN, and switch configuration for 20+ offices, APC battery backup support.

Replaced, deployed, imaged, re-imaged, and performed break fix tasks on desktops, laptops, and tablets on Windows XP, Vista, and Win 7.

Troubleshot automated tasks at login for doctors, nurses, transcriptionists. Supported Dictaphone devices and other peripheral devices for doctors and nurses.

Configured and supported security camera operations in building.

Hands-on printer support for 20+ offices, toner replacement, and any hardware problem.

Maintained and updated software documentation for end users.

Maintain, track, and order IT department inventory.

### Help Desk Technician

Northern Michigan University

Jan 2009 - May 2010 (1 year 5 months)

Provided exceptional customer service and technical support for staff members, faculty, and students.

Outlook troubleshooting and email backup, introduction to MS Exchange.

Repaired University owned laptops for both students and employees.

Deployed necessary software for students and faculty.

### **Education**



# Northern Michigan University

Bachelor's Degree, Business Computer Information Systems 2008 - 2012

### Skills

Computer Science • IT • System Administration • IT Support • Web Development • Web Content Writing • Software and Hardware • Outdoor Adventures